# NDZALAMA MABASA

WEB DEVELOPER

🔁 ndzalamabasa@gmail.com

**Q** 076 447 7729

I am a Full-Stack Web Developer with experience in Web Apps development, API Design, Database Design and implementation, Web Design and e-commerce development.

I believe a great website or web application should be easy to interact with and be accessible to everyone.

# **EDUCATION**

## **Umuzi Academy**

National Certificate in Information Technology (System Development) (SAQA ID 48872)

April 2022 - Present

## **University of Venda**

**Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Mathematics** 

Dec 2019

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Junior Tech Lead

**Umuzi Academy** 

Oct 2022 - Present

#### Junior Web Developer

**Strawberry Connect** 

May 2021 - Sep 2021

### Web Dev & Graphic Designer

Freelancing

Mar 2020 - Apr 2021

# **SKILLS**

## **Programming Languages and Tools**



































Portfolio Website

<u>mabasan</u>